So people are saying, well, if people would actually plan real protests, then they could
stop shaming the No Kings protests.
Okay, so what I want to bring to the attention is that folks have been in resistance for
a very long time.
Okay.
Black Lives Matter grassroots, specifically Black Lives Matter grassroots.
Code Pink.
I just named three different organizations from three completely different demographics
that organize consistently actual resistance.
And if you feel it is safe to do so without exposing or harming them, please drop any other
organizations in the comments.
The reason that you don't know about those organizations is because they perform actual
resistance.
They don't have the funding and they don't have the mainstream media support of a No Kings
protest, which is supported by Zios and Demos.
And when you have mainstream media support and the support of two groups that are actively
complicit in the ruling class suppressing the people, then you should ask yourself, what
am I supporting?
Again, it doesn't mean that you can't glean and gain something out of it, but it means that
you have to acknowledge that what you are involved in is not an act of resistance by nature of
it being supported by mainstream and the ruling class.
So that in addition, you do acts of resistance, because if that is the actual goal, then you have
to actually do that.
What's going to save everybody in this nation is actual resistance.
However, what's going to save only somebodies in this nation is performative.
And that is what has always been the case in this nation is that people will perform just
enough for themselves and they will not put themselves in any level of inconvenience for
anyone else.
And don't even fix your mouth to ask me what level of inconvenience I've put myself at.
I was on an HBO show and now you see me here selling pins that I package in my house.